(phone ringing)
- They don't look at, but who don't look at them?
(upbeat music)
- Hi, Andy.
- Hey, Andy.
- Welcome to Drop Is Alive, everybody.
- Where's the guy from last week?
He was great.
- He's been fired.
- What?
- Broke Smith's conduct.
- Really?
- That's true.
(laughing)
- With who?
- With whom?
- I can't believe that.
- Sorry sir.
- With who?
- Who ranked it?
- He was found ball's maxing in an area that wasn't permissioned.
Yeah, right.
- So, are you aware of this country's slander loss?
(laughing)
- I think a box cost is fine, isn't it?
- No, that's libel if it's a podcast, yeah.
- Yeah, and if it's on the Patreon, it's not libel.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- No, look, thank you very much
for your brilliant cover session last time.
- You were really good.
Have you seen it?
- I've watched it.
- Have you?
- I found it.
- I thought it was very good.
I thought it was quite well organized
and, you know, it was quite clean.
- I felt like it was missing something.
It was missing chaos, wasn't it?
- Yeah, but at this point in the recording,
we were ready into it, so that was quite nice.
- Well, fair point, Dan.
Thank you.
Welcome to Drop us a Line, our audience feedback show.
I should say, because I've been away,
I haven't had quite as much time as normal to triage
or the emails, so I'm afraid it's not going to be
quite as smooth as normal.
So, I hope that's all right.
- As normal referring to last time,
or that my baseline is going to be worse than that.
- Okay.
- Promises, promises.
(laughing)
- We're going to plum new depths.
- Let's get into it.
- Come on, let's do it.
- Right, what do you want first?
Some get yourself off the hook?
- Yeah, sure.
- I've had a few of those.
- Okay.
- And we've got a lot of, I'm actually these.
And I meant to send you a sound file
before we started.
It doesn't matter, okay.
(laughing)
- Nadi Kemp Safey writes,
"I'm listening to episode six or two.
I was troubled to hear you say
that despite belly dancing,
being a quintessential Egyptian dance,
Egyptian women basically don't do this now."
Nadi says, "I can't express how wrong you are about this."
- Oh, well, but then she does nobody.
(laughing)
- She does.
- "I'm from the city of the dead.
I'm from the city of the dead,
the medieval cemetery slum in the center of Cairo.
I can assure you, every single girl in my family
and all the neighbouring families
learn to belly dance from as soon as they can walk."
- That's very cool.
- It's not funny.
Look at little toddler doing a belly dance.
- You're always really excited
because we got someone who wrote him from Seattle
or something, but I think this is a really, really exciting place
- Jenner in the air from.
- And when there are special occasions,
the families will belly dance on mass in the streets.
Nadi says, "I would go so far as to say
it is socially awkward not to have learned to belly dance
by the time you're a teenager."
- Mm-hmm, interesting.
- So there are more sort of pro belly dance
as warriors in European,
but that's because these European women are considered
more marketable and exotic,
but across the class structure of Egypt,
belly dancing is a crucial
and completely uncontroversial pastime.
So hands up.
- Yeah, fair enough, that way.
- It's a shame I wasn't on this show
'cause I have belly dance.
- You have belly dance.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- When? - Gosh.
- Many years ago, at least 15, maybe 20 years ago.
- And how long did you keep it up for?
- Excuse me.
(laughing)
- It was exciting, but it wasn't that exciting.
- Sorry, sorry.
(laughing)
- I did it just one time at a hotel.
It was in tune this year.
I think where you've recently been,
but the hotel brought in some belly dancers
and then they dragged up the least interested looking person
and stew some belly dancing.
- Lovely. - I got picked on.
- And you got picked.
- Nice.
- All right, let's plow on.
On we plow, Effie Goetier.
- Don't know where she's writing from.
- Okay.
- Canada or France?
- Pointly.
- North Africa.
- Madagascar.
- French Guiana.
(laughing)
- Reunion.
- Well, we could dance this dance all day,
but Effie writes, just to let you know,
the fact on the most recent little fish
about speeding finds, do you remember this one?
- Oh.
- You can break them all once in Australia,
but you can do all sorts of stuff in India, for example.
- And you would be charged to say matmati.
- Yeah, yes, yeah.
- You can be driving drunk while unwell and speeding
and all of those.
Anyway, apparently it's taken almost word for word
from a comedy routine by a comedian called
Azim Banatwala.
- Oh, dear.
- So, and I've looked it up and it's absolutely true.
And I don't know whether it's just extraordinary
coincidence or whether we need to contact the ombudsman.
- So anyway, just...
- Well, apologies to that comedian.
I don't know them, are they?
- No, I didn't know me, but I looked at it.
It's very, it's a very good routine.
- They sound like it would be a perfect fish guest.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, we should get an invite out.
- Okay.
- Well, there we go.
- What a cool way to meet a guest.
- Yes.
- By stealing the material.
- The material in using it.
- That's all right, fantastic.
- Let's start with an apology and then see.
(laughing)
Right, now I'm gonna bring us out of the,
get yourself off the hooks.
- Okay. - And into the related water of,
I'm actually, right?
So you know, like, 'cause it's sort of,
it's bonus information.
We've said something slightly incorrect,
but it's not a get yourself off the hook.
- No, I'm interested, Andy,
that that actually is quite a good segue.
And I wonder if you feel in a bit under pressure this week.
- I never feel under pressure on the show.
(laughing)
No, I do.
I'm constantly, I pressure myself to do better for you guys.
- And for you guys listening and watching at home.
- Or wherever you are.
- Oh my God.
- Okay.
- Or wherever you are.
- No, stop it.
- We were doing so well.
You see what happens?
- Michael Bulter.
- From Perth, Australia.
- Uh-huh.
- Had a good giggle through the latest episode of "Drop us a Line."
But paused when I heard Andy, bizarre, and Anna weird.
These are the words we used, not us.
Express surprise at the entrance exam for medical school,
not testing medical knowledge.
Curious to hear your thoughts are an alternative model
where the entrance exam, presumably extensively tests medical knowledge.
I imagine people might want to prepare for such a test
and seek out institutions who will teach them such knowledge.
Maybe they could call that calls a medical knowledge degree.
- I'm not actually aware of this section though.
- We mentioned, oh it's weird that the entrance exam
for medical school doesn't test your medical knowledge.
And Michael is simply pointing out
that's the point of going to medical school
is to learn the medical knowledge.
So it's good to get in.
You shouldn't be expected to know how to diagnose strap throat.
We had someone who said that they refused to get an answer right
because the answer was Mark Twain as it was and so funny it was too.
So that's Michael just picking us up on that.
- Okay.
- Feels like we were on the hook actually there.
- What do you think they're testing then?
I know that they're just testing your general intelligence.
- Are you a good bloke?
- Yeah.
- Or lady bloke?
(laughing)
- Or was the Australian word for a few of bloke?
- That's it, Sheila.
- Oh, Sheila.
- Are you a bonzer, Sheila or not?
- Yeah.
- Jackie from Portland, Oregon.
- Hello, Jack.
- Yeah.
- I had to pause the latest episode
after the story about Lyndon Johnson's Taylor.
- Remember this?
- I do remember that.
It was Anna talked about a phone call
that's in the White House archives
about Lyndby Johnson, no?
- He was going to get a suit fitted.
- Yeah.
- And Sam, you need to give me some more
around the phone call.
- That's exactly it.
James, you've put your finger right on it.
Does it work?
- I heard Anna say bum hole, so it's Jackie.
I would put money down that LBJ never said bum hole
in his life.
In the goal, he says bum, bum hole.
- Bung hole.
- Though most Americans say butt hole.
- Interesting.
- Isn't that interesting that I just,
when I sort of got the spirit of LBJ inside me then,
I just said bum hole.
- You went the bum hole.
- I didn't even think about it.
- Yep, that's very good.
That's interesting, 'cause yeah,
the only other time I can think of the word bum hole
being used is by beavers and butt head.
So beavers and butt head, then be Johnson,
and then that's it for me.
- And me just then.
- And you.
- But you kind of summoned him.
So maybe I was summoning beavers.
(laughing)
So yeah, we've had a lot of people tripping on this.
Goat Lord and Ryan Monahan,
who says that it is in the presidential library
and archive, whatever, 'cause we joke
that they'll be preserving.
- I see.
- 'Cause it's a group bit of a American history.
It doesn't know what they are.
- So what were the two characters who wrote it there?
- Ryan, Jackie, Ryan and Goat Lord.
- Okay.
- Lord.
- It's just, you really kind of just skimmed out
for Goat Lord.
- We have, of course, Goat Lord and Ryan Monahan.
(laughing)
That would be a really good sort of duo.
Like, you know, Cannon and Ball.
- Ryan and Goat Lord.
- Ryan Monahan, Goat Lord.
I think it works a way better if you give his full name.
- I think it would be good to have a game show
where you get two people.
And one of them is Ryan Monahan
and one of them is Goat Lord.
And you have to guess which is which.
- Based only on ask human questions.
- It's the one who's easy to take, Cadd.
(laughing)
- Oh, dear.
- Very good.
- It's a funny idea.
Which one is Ryan Monahan?
- Is it the one standing on two feet?
(laughing)
- Or the thing on the demon.
- Gareth from Bandstiple, currently out on a dog walk
listening to Little Fish really siding with the baddies
where James mentions the top of Hollywood bushes aren't spiky.
And I came across this, Killjoy Hollywood
replete with spiky tops, there's always one.
- Yeah, you do get them occasionally, how high was it?
- That's his holy email.
- Yeah, no, how high was the top of there?
- I don't know 'cause he didn't have a ruler
in the image or anything, or a measuring tape.
So he sent an image, but it's so close up
that it's just the top of a bush.
There's no contact.
Have you got it there for us to see?
- No, I didn't print it out.
- But I think what I'm saying is,
unless he's climbed up an enormous ladder to take that photo,
the fact that he's taken a close-up means
that it can be no more than seven feet off the ground.
- That's a really good point,
because Elizabeth Brown adds that Holly is spiky
until about four or five meters up.
This is something I learned from a friend working
with me in environmental education.
And on the holy bushes where we worked,
we could see the spiky descended at least 10 feet up.
That was American Holly.
But it's the thing called evolutionary anachronism,
which is where plants have characteristics
that they evolved alongside now extinct megafauna.
But they've still got the characteristic.
- Oh, it's really cool.
- Very cool.
- So does it.
- It kind of implies that there was an enormous
Holly eating animal that was three meters tall
that existed sometime in history.
- That's so cool.
- I know, that's, I love that stuff.
I love it.
- That's great.
- My favorite thing about that, if we're doing facts,
'cause we are a fact show, really.
- I always forget that on this show.
- But they have, I think there's a theory
that there must have been some very, very fast predator
in North America, like thousands and thousands of years ago,
because some of the antelopes and stuff
have evolved to run so fast
that there must have been a predator
that was running faster as fast as them.
- It's stunning.
But don't we have cheaters and things?
In North America, not so much.
- Oh, of course, yeah, yeah.
- You do have cougars and stuff,
but they tend to be in the South.
This is like a bit further now.
- That's such exciting detective work.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- That's where your journey begins looking for an animal.
You guys ready to have your minds blown?
- Sure, yeah, please.
- Rob Shanks.
- Oh my god, what a name.
- Right.
- Listen to this week's Little Fish,
where another listener pointed out,
musician Shaggy's real name is Orville,
and Scooby-Doo Shaggy's real name is Norville.
I looked into this and more.
It seems they're both named because of their messy hair.
But what I found more interesting
is that in the 2020 animated film Scoob,
the character of Shaggy is voiced by the comic actor
Will Forte.
- He's famous, isn't he?
- Yeah.
- And his real name is Orville Willis Forte the fourth.
That's brilliant.
There is a third Orville Norville.
What?
- That's really good.
- Yeah.
- That's stunning.
- Scoob.
- The Bassoon Lounge opens its doors.
- Does it?
- As Tom Greed writes,
just thought I'd answer James's question
from the recent podcast,
as I'm sure many others already have.
And actually Tom, quite a few people have.
What can you play on the piano with only one hand?
Okay.
French composer Maurice Ravel wrote a concerto
for Austrian pianist Paul Vickenstein,
and I looked up, yes, some relation.
He'd lost his right arm in the first world war,
and it's called the piano concerto for the left hand.
- Yeah.
- I did know about that actually.
- I was gonna bring him up today
in our episode that we're recording later.
Yeah, 'cause we're talking about the piano later.
- He was a prisoner of war, some kind of war.
- He was a prisoner of war, lost his arm.
Older brother of Ludwig,
and he got a lot of musicians to write pieces for him,
and then he became quite a controversial character
in the music world,
because he would slightly rewrite their pieces
to make it work and really piss them off.
And then he would claim a sort of ownership
over these pieces as well.
But it was a piano that was invented
where he had pedals and so on, allowed for him to play
seemingly impossible pieces with one hand.
- And I think when he was a prisoner of war,
did he create like a fake piano and would just practice,
like it was just wood, it didn't make any sound,
but he practiced his finger in and stuff.
- That's so cool.
- So yeah, it was a word this guy,
but it wasn't the first thing that came into my head,
I must say. - That was fair enough.
And we've also had correspondents
from Benjamin Venkovsky on this,
James Finney Anzli and Goat Lord.
- So Benjamin is prolific, isn't he?
- Benjamin points out.
There was apparently a syllabus up to grade five
for one-handed piano students.
- Right. - Pretty cool.
- That is interesting.
- Yeah, in fact, I would say like thinking back at it now,
of course people who only have one hand can play piano,
and it was wrong of me to suggest that they couldn't.
- You didn't even say that.
You just said, I don't know, you know,
what are you playing with one hand, you know?
- Of course there were at the piano, of course.
- Yeah, that's fair enough.
- Hey, I've brought an item in.
- Ooh.
- Do you mind if I bring it to the table quickly?
- Sure.
- Please get it out.
- Well, I just, I forgot to bring this in
when I got in Balls Maxing.
- Yeah.
- And we have.
(laughing)
- Wonder what?
- What's that?
Wonder what you didn't need a chair today, then.
(laughing)
- I forgot that I had this,
and I saw it on my desk this morning,
so I brought it in.
So you mentioned Chinesia that I was there recently,
I just got recently got back from Chinesia.
I forgot that when we arrived at the hotel,
there was this amazing moment where Finella
just like grabbed me and went, oh my God, it's hot-dannn.
(gasping)
Right?
(laughing)
And they're sitting on a table
as part of a hotel book exchange.
People finish their books and they leave it.
- We saw this.
- Oh, Dr. Daniel.
- Dr. Daniel.
- It's incredible, this is a, what it looks like, a German.
- Is this a medical book?
- If no, this has five books in it,
all to do with Dr. Daniel and his family.
(speaking in foreign language)
- Oh, is that a sexy one?
- Yes.
- It's a romantic book.
- Oh my God.
- Yeah, Dr. Daniel, hot-dannn, it's met us.
- Immediately as we got there.
- I love that hot-dannn has become a thing
in your family life now.
- Your marriage.
(laughing)
- It's not good, is it?
- The one's been dreaming.
- This is absolute filth.
- Are you speak Kavetta German, Andy?
- Well, I don't know these words.
- Well, I translate this. - These are one on the GCSE syllabus.
They're telling that much.
I translated 'cause there's five books in there.
The first book is called, "My child belongs to me."
Betrayed in abandoned, but Claudia goes her own way.
That's book one. - That's good.
- Dr. Daniel's doing all this stuff, crumbs.
- That's a good point though.
Phinella has been saying hot-dannn when she sees hot-dannn stuff.
- Just men.
- Just men out there.
- I need them. - I need them.
- I don't even have beers and glasses.
They're just, yeah.
- General men.
- But even my middle child, Ted.
He's saying, "I've seen a hot-dannn."
- Well, we were by the pool and this guy walked by
who was really like built and Ted pointed at him
and said, "Why can't you look like that?"
And Phinella said, "Don't body shame your dad."
He's, he's fine.
Ted was like, "Okay, but then Ted's really into it.
He really wants me to work out to the point
where he got the message from Phinella,
but he couldn't stop subtly doing it."
and at one point he went, "Hey, dad, I was downstairs
"by the shop in the hotel.
"There's a gym right next to it.
"How weird."
And left it at that.
- Left it at that.
- Just like, "Oh, just if you want to check it out."
- There's a gym.
- That's cool, isn't it?
- Wow, yeah, anyway.
- Meanwhile, your other child is watching
a video of us talking about her now.
It's 50,000 times in a week.
- I went to visit Dan this weekend.
- Did you?
- And Dan was like, "It's Uncle James
"to his youngest kid."
And he was just non-plussed, obviously.
But then he went, "No, no, from the video
"and he showed him the headnet video
"and the kid just looked to me and went,
"Oh, like I was the most famous person on earth."
- He was properly star struck.
- That's so exciting.
Because when you find out someone from the,
you're tiny and you find out someone from the TV is real,
it's like finding out Spider-Man's real, you know?
- Yeah, exactly.
- I was like, "Boodle, it's the hairnet guy."
(laughing)
- I love it.
- Yeah.
- Should we have an email?
- Let's come to "Extreme Fish."
- We've had some unbelievably good extreme fish.
- Who?
- Lilith Wangsrad, who says in brackets,
pretend you're throwing up when you pronounce the guard.
So I hope that was all right, Lilith.
I work as a porter and a cleaning lady at a hospital.
While I work, I listen to you guys.
That means you've all been with me
when I've cleaned up blood in operation rooms
and you have walked with me
when I've had to take severed limbs to the morgue.
- Wow.
- Extreme fish.
- That is extreme fish.
- Andy Walker, from Birmingham, brackets,
not the Alabama one, sorry.
Doesn't matter, Andy.
Oh, Birmingham, Alabama.
- Yeah, so I thought that was a famous Andy Walker.
- He was from Alabama.
- No, Andy writes, from Birmingham.
My son, Ben Walker, age 12,
is a massive fan of no such thing as a fish.
He had to have a deciduous tooth extracted
at the dentist today as it hadn't come out on its own.
He chose to listen to fish the whole time
to distract him from the pain.
- Cool.
- That's pretty good.
- That is really cool.
- We are pain relief.
- Maybe he just listened to some of your outros
'cause they do say that one way to distract yourself
from pain is to get something even more painful.
- Yep.
- Well, Andy, it doesn't relate.
- That's, we can do them a compilation in future
if they've got any more surgery coming out.
- A compilation of my outros.
- Yeah.
That's a funny idea.
- It's a good service.
- Yeah.
Ron Jay of Germany writes,
we've been listening to fish for a few years.
We're on rotation number four now.
- Cool.
Very cool.
- We have a potential entry for extreme fish
as the podcast recently accompanied us
into the delivery ward.
- Hey.
- We were listening to fish before and during
the birth of our son Jonathan last month.
- Wow.
Congratulations.
- Congratulations.
- Amazing, congrats.
- Yeah.
- Why'd you call him Jonathan and not Dan, James, Andy.
- Anna.
- All four.
- Maybe they were listening to the episode
where we talked about Jonathan the Tartus,
the world's oldest Tartus.
- That'll be it.
- Yeah.
- And thought, how that's a good name.
- It's a really nice tribute.
Thank you, Ron.
- Well, there's middle names that might still be added.
So if you want to give Jonathan--
- Yeah, you probably do have time.
I don't know what the German rules are about
when you're allowed to put in middle names until--
- Looks, it doesn't matter.
What happened?
There's no pressure.
Johanna Koivunin writes that she nominates herself
to be the prawn queen.
- Ah, yes.
- Oh, okay.
- So that's the best.
Again, I wasn't in the show,
but it's like the best mess.
People are allowed to nominate themselves
by having the best email.
- Yeah, it's not like the no bells.
I think we're not a strict.
We haven't had the demand of the no bells.
- No, but the idea was that we would look through
all that I've been sent in.
Maybe after a few months and decide, you know?
- Well, Johanna's nominating herself
because she lives in Sweden and would have been excited
to attend your live show in Lund.
But you have unconsideringly scheduled it
a week after I'm expected to give birth.
And I expect fish will be playing at some point during birth.
And I feel like it then do with the probably gross crown
that comes with the title.
- Okay.
- So Johanna, there's no crown
that comes with the title prawn queen.
- Tell you what, there will be if you name one of your kids.
- After us.
- We missed the boat with Jonathan.
- Yeah.
- But we could have some influence here.
- Dan James, Anna, Andy or Goat Lord.
- One of those times and you are prawn queen.
- Yeah, thanks but no thanks.
- Okay.
- Yep.
- Will writes, "I was wondering if any elf
has ever had the idea of a QI museum,
but a real physical one.
With all the amazing range of things we've been shown
from unopenedable tins of fish and enigma machines
to James's latest purchase of silk papal socks."
- Hmm.
- "I know it would be a really popular
and fascinating place to visit.
Are there ready plans?"
- Well, no.
- But.
- I have.
The reason I brought them is for the quiz that we're doing
later, they're going to be a prize.
- Right.
- You're going to give away your Pope-Sauce papal
my holy socks.
You said, "Only the Pope's allowed white ones."
- Yeah.
- Wow.
- Where these, and you will too, will become Pope-Sauce.
- Can I feel them?
Can we feel them?
- They may feel a halt like do you get something from them?
Do you get the odor of sanctity?
- The Holy Spirit enters you.
- They smell so beautiful now.
They smell so, like, give 'em a whiff.
They smell so, they're fragrance.
- Oh, they are fragrance.
- And they're cool.
- Amazing prize for the quiz.
That's so good.
- Those are the highest qualities socks I've ever seen.
Yeah, they're pretty cool.
- They're very cool.
- But yeah, on the, thanks, but no thanks of a museum.
- Oh, yeah, sorry, yeah, yeah.
- "I have long thought that a museum of things
that you buy off eBay that have kind of cool stories
behind them would be really good."
- We're all looking at you, don't you?
- So we could have a little room, like a little museum.
I went to a crab museum this weekend in Margate.
And it's only a room or two, right?
It's not that big.
But you could just have, like, one of the stamps
from the, when the boat's got stuck in the red sea.
'Cause you buy them off eBay for 30 quid.
You put the stamps there, and then you click a button,
and it plays you, I was talking about the facts
that's related to it.
- Yeah, that's a really good idea.
- That's very nice.
Do you have over the years of fish?
I have bought random things related to our show,
same as James.
I am, I was sort of, there was noise of me doing
my little comedy museum at my house,
and that's when you shut down the museum.
Well, it turns out we would have no visitors.
Ted's lobbying you to turn the place into a gem anyway, so.
- Exactly.
- I didn't know you were going to invite everyone
around to your house to look at your stuff.
- Yeah, yeah, it's a fact that I was not keen.
- It's a fact that I was not keen, yeah.
I mean, I would say just rent out a small spot
and do a pop-up rather than telling everyone where you live.
- Yeah, would you do it in the garden, Chad?
- Yeah, no, that's where we were thinking of doing it.
- Yeah, it's Chad.
- People don't need to know that's where you live.
You sleep there occasionally,
when Fener's got a bit tired of the whole thing,
or when hot down is visiting, of course,
but you can just say, like, go to the shed,
and then put in brackets, this is not where Dan lives.
- Yeah, yeah.
I think that'll deal with it.
- Yeah, I almost got a massive argument
off the back of a purchase I tried to know the other day.
You tell me if I'm crazy, all right?
It was a golden pen, not real gold, a golden pen.
Now, you know Peter Sellers.
He was pink Panther Inspector Clueso.
He was in the Goons Show.
- It was a gold pen.
- You're poor, why?
- That Peter Sellers gifted to his uncle,
(laughing)
which was then used to sign a sale document
of the hotel that Faulty Towers was based on,
but decades after it stopped functioning as a hotel.
- Here's why I would say,
like before we make a judgment
on whether you're insane or not,
if it was like 25p, I say go for it.
- Yeah.
- How much was it?
- Would you be willing to go up to 200 pounds?
- I knew it was going to be 200 pounds.
- What's the margin of?
- Sorry, this pen that Sellers gave his uncle.
- gave it to his uncle.
- Was later used to sign a document selling,
not the hotel in Faulty Towers,
just the one it was based on.
I think your museum is going to be really nice then,
because I think you'll have the item in the case.
And so often, the little thing next to it
just says like Roman coin or whatever.
It doesn't quite show.
But you're going to have to have the biggest information board
next to every item in the museum.
The audio guide is going to be like 10 days long.
- Oh God.
- Okay, well, that, you know.
- I'm on Fence side.
And I am in almost every item that you have.
But in this one, in particular.
- Yeah, I'm on Fence side.
You think the replica pens are not going to sell
like hotcakes in the museum shop?
I'm going to make that back in the first day.
replica pens that Peter Sellers gave to his uncle.
- Does the pen is like not real gold, right?
- No, not real gold.
- Apart from that, what does it look like?
It just looks like a pen.
- Oh, it looks like a pen, yeah.
- Yeah, yeah.
- But the pens you'll be selling in the gift shop
will be real gold, right?
But you'll sell them in a big discount to get the,
you've got to prime the pump, haven't you?
- Exactly.
- You can have a big area of your gift shop
called Big Sellers.
But it's named after Peter Sellers.
(all laughing)
- That's pretty good.
You can have a sign on the way and saying,
"Hey, Big Spenders."
But it's about Steven Spender, the 20th century poet.
- What's he doing in my museum?
- I don't know, God knows Stan.
Did he maybe once bump into George Harrison at a party?
- Steven Spender.
- Yeah.
- Well, his daughter married Barry Humphreys
of whom is going to be a very big part of the museum.
So yeah, actually, well done, he's in.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
- It's like a superpower, but also a disease.
- A lot of them are.
- Yeah.
- It's like you were bitten by a radioactive twat.
(all laughing)
- Dallon, all twat.
- I just wish I hadn't said Dallad over twat
'cause now that's not usable.
- I found him, they were quite loud with Dallad.
I think the manager would come across.
- All right, now, this is something off the back
of your normal book, James.
- Okay.
- So you guys had your funny books that you were doing,
but mine would just be a normal book.
- Yep.
Emma Werner writes, "Andy says that this is a clear book
"of contender, your a normal book."
And Emma just wants to say she looked into the history
of the man Booker Prize, the book's prize,
which of course is named after the prize's original sponsor,
the cash and carry outlet, Booker Group.
Founded by Richard and George Booker in 1835.
- That's cool.
- I know, sorry to the whole fish team,
but it does mean that it's time for,
oh, ready?
- What's this?
♪ It's T-T-A-U-M-A-A-P-R-T-A-F-O-Q-U-E ♪
♪ Things that are unexpectedly named after a person
"rather than a functional quality."
♪ Unexpected epinems, N-S-T-A-A-F-F-F-F-F ♪
- Okay, I like the production value.
I think that's the classiest thing I've ever heard.
- That was great, that was an infomercial.
- It was, yeah. - And it was sent in by Tom Hewitt.
Can I hear it again?
- Yeah.
♪ It's T-T-A-U-M-A-P-R-T-A-F-O-Q-U-E ♪
♪ Things that are unexpectedly named after a person
"rather than a functional quality."
♪ Unexpected epinems, N-S-T-A-F-F-F-F-F-F-F-F ♪
- What I like about it is 'cause halfway through,
it goes P-A-R-T.
And you think it's gonna be hard to eat?
- It just goes F-O-Q. (laughing)
- Yeah. - Love it.
- That's great. - That's excellent.
- Just magic. - Yeah. - Thank you to Tom Hewitt.
- Is that how you're gonna begin every book pitch meeting
that you have? (laughing)
- Yes. (laughing)
- That's gonna play and you're gonna make your entrance
like a wrestler into the room. - Absolutely, yeah.
- I just think that's magic.
Thank you so much, thank you so much, Tom.
Look, there are quite a few of these this week,
but they're all going in the book.
So don't worry, the Gaman Bomb says Joel Smith,
named after Captain RS Gaman, does not contain Gaman.
I like that.
- And might you expect that it would contain Gaman?
(laughing)
- Is it, I mean, what is it?
It's just a bomb, right? - It's just a bomb.
But the Gaman Bomb does a population trend
or something, doesn't it?
- It does. - Oh, I see, yeah.
- I suppose. - Like the baby boomers
could be called the Gaman Bomb to a degree.
- Is that what this is?
Because I thought it was,
because I don't really, that's not what it is.
It's a bomb. - No.
- Yeah, but it's not a Gaman Bomb.
I think you sound like it's named after a functional quality,
like it's a heavily salted bomb.
Or, you know what I mean?
Like it's a bomb that contains Gaman.
- The Gaman Bomb.
- Yeah.
- If it was called the pork, the pork ballistic missile,
you'd think it would have blown a pork in it, you know?
- I don't think that was. - I don't know what it was.
- Okay.
- They can't all be seconds,
and I'll put it in the second half of the book, okay?
Put it in the second half. - Not too near the end.
It's going to be hidden kind of about 70% through.
- Absolutely.
I've got to hide the broccoli under a potato there.
- The Gaman.
- You've got to hide the Gaman in the middle of the sandwich.
- Dammit.
- Yes.
No, that's fair enough here.
Well, I'll just add, I'll just add then,
Pim Hene from New South Wales, right?
That there's a sock knitting technique
for knitting the heel,
'cause we've been on your socks, James,
called the Strong Heal.
As you can guess, it is named for its creator,
Gerdean Crawford Strong.
So, that's good.
- But it sounds like it's where making your heel spooker.
That's very good. - That's very good.
- Oh, so that's a good one.
- That's what we'll bang on first.
- I think so, yeah.
- Put that on the first page, that's it.
- It's not first page.
- I'm sorry to say, I think it is.
- Okay.
- I feel like this book might be very second half heavy.
- It's all second half.
- It's three pages, isn't it?
- Right.
- Now it's time for the second half.
- I've got 300 of these things now.
- Try one more just to see if,
I wanna see if you've gone mad.
- Okay.
- And you can't spot what your own book is anymore.
- I'm too close to it.
- Like the Sistine Chapel, Michelangelo,
you know, you couldn't see it
'cause he was so far up there.
(laughing)
David.
David Henderson.
No location given.
I hope you are well.
I was wondering if you're aware of the Chicago-based blues
and R&B record label, Chess Records.
- You guys have heard of Chess Records, right?
- I have actually.
- Howl and Wolf, Muddy Waters, Buddy Guy,
many amazing artists recorded with Chess Records.
It was founded by two Polish brothers,
Leisure General, Chiz, and Fugel, Chiz.
They anglicized their name on "Pompcoming to the USA"
and most assumed the label has a connection
to the game of Chess.
- Did they?
- Specifically, their logo is a chessboard.
The logo of Chess Records is a chessboard.
It looks chessy, but it's actually just named after the brothers.
- Then why would you think it was associated with Chess, really?
It's not like none of the songs was about Chess.
- Their surname was Records.
- At least.
I think Chess had his good chessboard in the logo.
That was the end of the first half.
- Honestly, Andy, I think this is now subsuming you so much.
It's like, when did you first realize
that Andy had gone completely mad?
Well, it was when he compared his stupid book
with Michelangelo painting the Sistine Chapel.
- I would say that was the moment
when I thought maybe this has gone too far.
- Yeah.
It's when we got a call from his family saying,
he's in the corner of the room just singing this weird jingle
over and over and over.
- I've listened to that so many times.
- I bet you have.
- It was so true.
- Yeah, I think he've lost it, Andy.
But it's okay, we're here for you.
- I'm not here to be here for you.
- What?
- I don't care that you're here for me.
I am following my own path.
- Sure.
- I'm not here anymore.
- You're here for me, but I'm already over there.
- Where are you?
- I am.
- When this show ends because my book has become so successful
that you guys are just sick of like the crowds outside,
waiting every week with more suggestions
for the sequel book.
- What are you talking about?
Even if it is successful,
you have given 5,000 people 10% each of the book.
If anything, you're in debt for the rest of your life.
Paying this amount back.
- Yep.
- That's a fair point.
That's a fair, I shouldn't have put it in the email
also reply that you just really mailing
about whatever subject get 10% of this book.
- Yeah.
- Oh, dear.
You know there's a lot of an old normal wisdom film.
- Is it really?
- Yeah, I think it might be traveling store.
He gives about 11 or 12 people 10% of an idea.
And then he has to work extra jobs to make up for it.
Very funny.
- It's a funny idea.
He was a funny guy.
Apparently he was a terrible sex past though.
- No!
- Well, that is ruining quite a large section of my museum.
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh, no.
The corner of wisdom.
- I've heard that.
Yeah.
Norman Foley should have been called.
Anyway, that's it for this week.
On Draws Align.
(upbeat music)
- Well, thanks guys.
- You're very welcome.
- That was a really fun show.
I had a brilliant time.
I hope you guys had an alright time.
- Well, we got through it, I would say.
- Yeah.
- Any feedback for yourselves on how you could
enjoy it more next time?
- I think just look back at your predecessor.
- Yep.
- See what they did.
- Try and do something a bit more like that.
- Your outro was unbelievably good last time.
It made me realize what this show could be.
- I learned from the best.
Sandy Talkswake and Stephen Fry.
(laughing)
- Well, I'll close it now and I'll do it
just as well as you did last time.
- I'll go for it, man.
- That's it for this episode.
- Wait here for you.
- Okay.
- That's it for this episode of Drops of Line.
If you've got thoughts, comments, feedback, please send them
to, don't, don't nod.
To this importantly.
- Why?
- 'Cause it makes me giggle.
- Oh, okay.
- Sorry, Dan was trying to throw me off for listeners at home.
Or wherever you're looking to the show.
Listen them all out.
Thank you for listening to Drop of the Line.
- Where are you looking at?
- Camera's over there, mate.
(laughing)
- It's just, it's just, (laughing)
I was trying to look sort of,
I was trying to look kind of within
to kind of get a grip on myself.
Stop myself crying with laughter.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I think it might be something wrong with my eyes.
Like every show I end up crying with laughter.
- It's still part of the actual.
(laughing)
- So, um,
so it's forecasted a queue I don't know,
it's the email address to write to.
If you've got grist that you want to contribute
to the mill of the next episode of Drop of the Line,
we'd love to hear from you.
Thank you to everyone who's written in today.
I'm sorry we weren't able to read all your emails out,
but we had a good go.
And, um, that's it.
We'll be back in the fortnight with another of these,
who'll be hosting.
Not me, I'll be over there.
- It will be you.
- I'll do it.
And gladly.
Bye.
(upbeat music)